

9707 Sugar Hill Dr. Austin, TX 78748

emilydevoll.com

emilydevollart@gmail.com

214-794-0328



QUIRKY. CREATIVE. FUN.

Austin-based UI/UX Designer who strives to master the art of web design by harmonizing structure and clean lines with bold colors and creative flare.

My understanding and love of design has been instilled in me since birth, my education from Oklahoma State University set my foundation in research, but it is attending The Iron Yard that has taught me to combine these tools to create a better online experience for people of all ages.





Detail Oriented

Written Communication

Team Player

Dedicated

Empathetic



August 2015 - November 2015

3 Month Intensive Immersion Program

Course: User Interface Design

EDUCATION

OKLAHOMA STATE UNIVERSITY

August 2008- May 2011

Major: Human Development &

Family Sciences

Focus: Child & Family Services International Studies Minor: Clubs: Pi Beta Phi Sorority

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop

HTML5

CSS3

Sass

jQuery

InVision



PREVIOUS JOB EXPERIENCE



Jim & Heather Trungale Adobe Illustrator

September 2014 - September 2015

Nanny/Personal Assistant

I was a personal assistant and nanny to a 4 year old and a new born, premature baby. I learned what it is like to work with one "reoccuring" client" and the skills necessary to insure their continued satisfaction.

RICHARDSON INDEPENDENT SCHOOL DISTRICT

August 2012 - August 2014

PACE Site Coordinator

State Licensed Child Care Director at 2 elementary schools in Dallas/ Richardson, TX. This position entailed: hiring/training new employees, developing lesson plans for grades K-6th in all school subject areas, collecting weekly tuition/filling out deposits, enforcing disciplinary procedures, attending monthly Site Coordinator meetings, adhering to all licensing regulations, submitting employee time sheets, while creating a positive rapport with all parents, students, and school staff.

EXPERIENCE WITH

User Personas User Flows Wireframes Style Tiles Mockups Responsive Design

Mobile Applications

RICHARDSON INDEPENDENT SCHOOL DISTRICT

May 2009 - August 2012

Technology Department Summer Intern

Every summer while in college I interned with the Tech Dep. performing: tech equipment prep/assembly/repair, secretarial duties, and running the summer robotics camps. This is where my love for tech began.